再也不必踏遍世界寻找完美礼物啦
Now you don't have to search the world for the perfect gift.
传统工艺  手工制作
Handmade in the tradition of ancient artists...
-长草娃娃  -全新长草娃娃宠物
- Ch-ch-ch-chia! - ...It's new chia pets!
长草象娃娃  牛娃娃  还有小狮崽
Chia elephant, chia cow, and chia lion cub.
步骤简单
It's easy.
将长草娃娃在水里泡一晚  撒上种子...
Soak your chia overnight, spread the seeds...
点名
...Call roll.
阿卡先生
Mr. Aka.
矶鹞渡生活协助中心
...Resident of a Sandpiper Crossing facility
或是其他类似退休社区的居民
or similar retirement community,
你也许有资格获得补偿
you may be eligible to receive compensation.
矶鹞渡生活协助中心
Residents of some Sandpiper Crossing
或其他类似退休社区的居民
or similar retirement communities
可能因商品和服务被超额收费
may have been overcharged for goods and services.
与哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所合作
In partnership with the law offices of Hamlin, Hamlin & Mcgill,
戴维斯梅因律所致力于帮助
the law offices of Davis & Main are working to help those
被退休社区超额收费的居民
who have been overcharged by their retirement communities.
如需免费咨询
For your free consultation,
请拨打戴维斯梅因律所505-242-7700
Call Davis & Main at 505-242-7700.
505-242-770...
That's 505-242-770...
这是金·韦克斯勒的语音信箱  请留言
You've reached Kim Wexler. Please leave a message.
某天你会看见我*
*Someday, you'll see me
漂浮在灿烂阳光里*
*Floatin' in the sunshine
低飞的云朵里我探出头*
*My head stickin' out from a low-flyin' cloud
你会听见我呼唤*
*You'll hear me call you
歌声穿透阳光*
*Singin' through the sunshine
甜美清澈至极*
*Sweet and clear as can be
巴里海轻声细语*
*Bali ha'i will whisper
音乐剧《南太平洋》中的神秘岛屿"巴里海"
乘着海洋之风*
*on the winds of the sea
我在这儿  你的独特岛屿*
*Here am I, your special island!
到这儿来  到这儿来*
*Come to me, come to me!
巴里海  巴里海*
*Bali ha'i, bali ha'i
巴里海*
*Bali ha'i
好啦  就这样
All right, there you go.
为期一周的《南太平洋》音乐剧巡演到此为止
That completes our weeklong tour of "South Pacific."
不客气
You're welcome.
明天我们开始探索
Tomorrow we begin our exploration
卡朋特乐队的曲目
of The Carpenters' catalogue.
当然我也接受点歌  没错
Of course, I'm open to requests. That's right.
你只需要拨电话给我  随时欢迎
All you got to do is call me, any time.
好吗
All right?
再见
Uh...Bye.
打给我
Call me.
注意界限  阮女士
Boundaries, Mrs. Nguyen.
注意界限
Boundaries.
你在这儿干嘛  饭碗这么快就搞丢啦
Why are you here? You lose that job already?
我最好有那么幸运
I should be so lucky.
你不喜欢你的工作吗
You don't like your job?
可怜的孩子
Boo-hoo. Poor baby.
你可知道有些人忙于生计
You know, ‭some people work for a living.
可没人派给我们免费用车
No one gives us free cars.
-你到底来这做什么  -我付了这儿房租
- So why are you here?  - This place is paid up.
身为合法房客我有权利待在这
I'm within my rights as your legal tenant.
你只需要知道这点
That's all you need to know.
是咖啡香吗  你在煮咖啡吗
Do I smell coffee? Have you got a pot on?
怎么
Why?
帮我来一杯如何
How about a fill-up?
你自己买得起
You can afford to buy your own.
咖啡越早来  我就越快走
Faster I get coffee, the faster I'm out of here.
你好  女士们
Chào các cô, ladies!
该死的...
Son of a...
日间美容美甲
金柏莉·韦克斯勒
你东西还没有整理好
You haven't unpacked yet?
凯文和佩奇到了
Kevin and Paige are here.
没问题
Absolutely.
我不清楚查克具体跟你说了什么
I don't know exactly what Chuck may have said to you,
但你要知道  我并没有要求他帮我说话
but just so you know, i did not ask him to step in on my behalf.
你们好  抱歉久等
Hi, guys. Sorry for the wait.
-没关系  -你好
- Not a problem. - ‭Hi.
很高兴再次见到你
Wonderful to see you again.
-霍华德  -凯文
- Howard. - ‭Kevin.
你好  金  很高兴见到你们俩
Hi, Kim. ‭Good to see you two.
你好  佩琪  你好  凯文
Hi, Paige. Hi, Kevin.
金  很高兴见到你
Kim, ‭great to see you.
-请坐  -谢谢
- Please, have a seat. - ‭Thank you.
凯文  你孙子怎么样了
Kevin, how's your grandson?
管不住啊
Oh, outta control,
围着我们团团转
just running circles around all of us.
你好  有什么事吗
Hello. Can I help you?
你知道我为什么来吗
You know why I'm here?
他需要你的答复
He needs an answer.
不好意思  我不得不拒绝
Respectfully, ‭I'm gonna have to say no.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
确定
I am.
欢迎
法官大人  被告的请求很合理
Your honor, the defense has made the very reasonable request
请求原告公开医疗记录
that the plaintiffs produce their medical records
或已签字的HIPPA授权书
or, barring that, a signed HIPAA release
《健康保险流通与责任法案》
以便我方自行检查记录
so that we can examine the records ourselves.
法官大人  我方委托人的医疗记录
Your honor, ‭our clients' medical records
与此案内在是非毫无关联
have no bearing ‭on the merits of this case.
医疗记录与此案关联显著
The medical records are plainly relevant,
因为它们与我方观点联系紧密
as they bear directly on our contention that
即这些原告人并不能充分代表集体诉讼
the plaintiffs are not adequate class representatives.
这显然是想胁迫原告人
This is a transparent attempt at intimidation.
-仅此而已  -为什么
- Nothing more. - ‭How so?
我方委托人的医疗记录里
Many of our clients have information
大多都有不愿公开的隐私信息
in their medical records that they prefer to keep private.
他们和我们一样害怕
They're fearful, as any of us would be,
一群陌生人
at the thought of a bunch of strangers
偷看他们的私人资料
poking around ‭in their personal files,
如果强迫他们公开这部分信息
and by forcing them to reveal this information,
被告就是在胁迫他们撤诉
the defense is banking on them simply dropping out of the case.
法官大人  这只是集体诉讼确认而已
Your honor, this is about class certification. That's all.
如果名单中的原告人患有痴呆
If the named plaintiffs are suffering from dementia
或其他精神缺陷
or other mental deficiencies --
你是说他们没有行为能力吗
you're saying they're incompetent?
我是说为了集体诉讼确认
I'm saying we have the right to any record
我们有权获得证明原告
that would speak to their competency,
具备行为能力的任何资料
as regards this class-certification issue.
法官大人  被告方似乎想两者兼得
Your honor, it seems that the defense wants to have it both ways, then.
如果我方委托人患有痴呆
If our clients ‭are suffering from dementia,
那么他们最初和矶鹞渡签署住宿合同时
then the residency contracts they signed with Sandpiper
就不可能是知情的
couldn't have been entered into knowingly.
不不  我们不是这个意思
No, no. That is not what we're...
被告想声称
The defense wants to claim
居住者有能力签署合同
that their residents are competent enough to be held to their contracts
却没有能力起诉
but too incompetent to sue.
这不是很矛盾吗
So which is it?
许多居住者是很多年前签署合同的
Many of the residents signed their contracts years ago,
那时候他们完全有行为能力
and at the time, ‭they were perfectly competent.
但这是会变的
But that can change,
尤其是年岁已高的居住者
especially when we're talking about elderly individuals.
那么也许矶鹞渡专挑有精神疾病的老年人
Or maybe sandpiper preyed on mentally incompetent seniors
骗走了他们的钱财
and bilked them out of their money.
韦克斯勒小姐
Miss Wexler.
我只是在为我方委托人辩护
I am simply trying to defend our clients
免受被告方欺压
from bullying by the defense.
法官大人  正如您面前的报告中所述
Your honor, as stated in the brief in front of you,
这是个标准申请
this is a standard request,
在同类案件中均被允许
granted in every case of its kind.
这不是欺压
This is not about bullying.
允许这样的隐私侵犯
Granting this invasion of privacy
会让我们的委托人二次受害
allows our clients to be doubly victimized.
我请求您拒绝被告的动议  法官大人
I ask that you deny the defense's motion, your honor.
我倾向于允许这一申请
I'm leaning toward granting the motion,
但我想重读一下诉状和简述
but I would like to review the pleadings and briefs again.
我会很快答复你们
I'll have my decision for you shortly.
休庭
Adjourned.
回办公室再见
I'm gonna meet you back at the office.
韦克斯勒小姐  你好
Ms. Wexler. Hey.
我只想说  你刚才表现很好
I just wanted to say, good work in there.
谢谢  但我肯定输了
Thanks, but I -- I'm pretty sure I lost.
当然了  这种情况你赢不了的
Oh, of course you did. It's an unwinnable position.
所以你上司都懒得出面
That's why your boss didn't bother showing up.
但是你坚持不懈  虽败犹荣  我很欣赏
But you went down swinging, and I admire that.
谢谢
Thank you.
你午餐有什么安排
What are you doing for lunch?
可能就在自动贩卖机买点吧
Um, probably just grabbing something from the vending machines.
我们可以吃好一点嘛
We can do better than that.
斯韦卡特先生  很高兴见到你
Mr. Schweikart, good to see you, sir.
-你好吗  肖恩  -我很好
- Ah, how you doing, Sean? ‭- Very well.
要什么喝的  您还是要莫斯科之骡吗
Can I get some drinks for you two? Your usual Moscow Mule?
肯定的  你要吗
Absolutely. You want one?
全市最好的莫斯科之骡
Best Moscow Mule in the city.
新鲜的生姜  纯铜杯  很正宗
Fresh ginger, ‭real copper mug, the works.
真是复古  我不用了
That's very vintage, but I'm good.
冰茶就可以了
Just an iced tea.
你确定吗
You sure?
那好吧  我就独自做一个
All right, then. I'll be the sole degenerate
工作日中午喝酒的堕落汉吧
who's drinking ‭in the middle of a work day.
那也很复古了
That, too, is vintage.
我去让他们调
I'll get those started.
所以你在哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所十年了
So, you've been with HHM, what -- 10 years?
没错  去年八月满十年
Y-yeah, last August.
你是从收发室做起的吗
And you started in the mail room?
没错  我在那干了六年
I did. I was six years there.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
我问别人的  这地方很小
Oh, I asked around. It's a small town.
听上去你已经尽职尽责了
You know, it sounds like you certainly paid your dues.
我运气很好
I was very fortunate.
律所一边让我工作  一边供我读完法学院
HHM put me through law school while I worked.
他们很会培养人才啊
That's great that ‭they foster talent like that.
现在你给他们工作  就当还债是吧
And I imagine you're paying it off as part of your deal?
是的  我很乐意
Yeah, happily.
好多人都是这样的安排
It's a pretty standard arrangement.
我得说  今天看你在法庭上
I have to say, ‭watching you in court today,
确实勾起我不少回忆
it sure did bring back some old memories for me.
反正让我想起了一件事
One in particular, anyway.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - ‭Yeah.
我当时从法学院毕业一年  在波士顿一家律所
I was a year out of law school at this firm in Boston,
我终于接了第一个大案子
and I was finally put on my first big case --
一桩大型就业歧视案
This huge ‭employment-discrimination suit.
这案子让律所十年都有活干
That thing kept us in billing for a decade.
总之  我们接了这单大的
Anyway, we landed this monster,
而且我成为了预审听证时
and I find out I'm second chair to one of the partners
一位合伙人的助理律师
on the preliminary hearing,
我就想  "就是它了
and I think, "This is it.
"我之后的职业生涯全靠这一搏了"
"This is what will define the rest of my career."
听证会越来越近
So, the hearing's getting closer and closer,
我甚至买了一件负担不起的西装
I even get this new suit that I can't afford --
我分三张信用卡刷的
I split it over three credit cards.
可能现在还在还钱
I'm probably still paying it off to this day.
我一大早就去了  穿着我的新西装
So, I go in bright and early, I'm wearing my new suit,
准备桌上的材料  这时抗辩方走进来
prepping my table, and in walks the opposing counsel.
他们有四个人  一个高级合伙人
There's four of them -- one senior partner
还有三个高级律师
and three high-level associates.
我还没出生他们就开始干这行了
These guys have been litigating longer than I've been alive.
但我想的是  "没什么大不了的
But I think, "Mm, I'm good.
"我老板来了就没事了"
"I got my boss coming. It'll be fine."
我就一个人坐在桌前
So, I'm sitting alone, at my table,
等着老板现身
waiting for my boss to show.
我等啊等
And I'm waiting.
等啊等
突然  他们宣布开庭
And then, suddenly, ‭they're calling us to order,
我才意识到我的律所没人来
and I realize that no one from my firm is coming.
只有我一个
It's just me.
我心想  "好吧
So I think, "All right, then.
"是时候了"
"This is the moment."
我上前拼了老命地辩论
And I get up there, and I argue like my life depended on it.
汗流浃背  旁征博引
I'm sweating, and I'm citing statutes left and right.
我表现得还行
And I'm doing okay. Respectable.
但我这把BB枪难敌四架榴弹炮
But I'm just a BB gun to these four howitzers.
我当然输了
And I lose, of course.
不可避免
It was inevitable.
但之后我突然意识到
But later, it hit me
我的老板根本就没打算到场
that my boss never intended to show.
他们都一笑而过
And they all laughed about it.
拍着我背说  那是对我的考验
They patted me on the back, said it was my trial by fire,
我也跟他们一起笑  但你知道
and I laughed with them, but, you know,
我觉得很不好受
It never really sat well with me.
你需要他们的支持
You want them to have your back.
因为最后我才知道
Because at the end of the day,
那不是为了考验我的勇气
it wasn't about proving my mettle.
而是我老板不想错过高尔夫
My boss had a tee time that he didn't want to miss.
我在那儿没待多久
I wasn't there long.
可以问下你为什么叫我...来这吗
Could I ask why we... are here?
我已经注意你很久了
You know, I've had my eye on you for a while.
自从凯特尔曼一案开始
Since that Kettleman thing.
你真是为他搞定了一桩极好的案子
That was an excellent deal you got for him.
我想知道为什么
And I'm wondering why someone
一个可以搞定那一单的人
who could put together a deal like that
没有后援  明知要输  却还要辩护
is arguing a losing position with no backup.
我对哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所没有怨言
I have no complaints about HHM.
很好
That's great.
但是  如果你碰巧正在寻求改变
However, if on the off chance, if you're pondering a change,
斯韦卡特考科利会很乐意
Schweikart and Cokely would be more than happy
善用你的才华
to put your talents to good use.
当然我们得有更正式的会面
Of course, we'd have to have a more formal meeting,
讨论细节  但我们认为你会非常合适
work out specifics, but we think you would be a great fit.
我受宠若惊
Well, I'm -- I'm flattered,
但这明显存在职业道德问题
but there's clearly an ethical issue here.
当然是等你弄完矶鹞渡的案子
Well, of course, ‭we'd take you off Sandpiper.
你放心
And rest assured,
我们不想要哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所的
we wouldn't be expecting any information
任何策略信息
about HHM strategy.
我们是一家大规模多元化的律所
Look, we're a large, diversified firm.
想想你可以用我们的资源成就什么
And just think what you can do with our resources
可以自由地展翅翱翔
and the freedom ‭to really spread your wings.
这...
That's...
我亏欠哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所很多
I owe a lot to HHM.
学费债务吗  我们可以替你偿还
Your tuition debt? ‭We can take care of that.
真慷慨
That's very generous.
花点时间考虑一下
Well, give it some time to think about it.
你来电话  我们就安排会面
And you give me a call, and we'll set up a meeting
会见其他高级合伙人
with the rest of the senior partners.
先说清楚...
And to be clear...
我说的可是合伙人机会
I'm talking partner track.
天哪肖恩  你是在莫斯科调的酒吗
Jesus, Sean, what -- what'd you have to send to Moscow?
抱歉让您久等了  斯韦卡特先生
Sorry for the wait, Mr. Schweikart.
可以点餐了吗
Are we ready to order?
...梅斯向您推荐这款快速切菜机
...Mays here for the gourmet quick chop.
它可以十分快捷  简便  安全地
It's the fastest, easiest, and safest way
将蔬菜切碎或切块
to chop, mince, or dice any vegetable, guaranteed.
操作方法如下
Here's how it works.
放好蔬菜
Just place the vegetable on the board,
按下按键
give it tap
立刻就有了做沙拉用的细细切碎的卷心菜
and you've got finely shredded cabbage in seconds for crunchy coleslaw.
再按一下...
tap again and chop...
趴下
Get down. ‭
Get down.
要带什么话
What's the message?
收下那五千块
Take the $5,000.
这么一句话需要两个人来跟我说
It took two guys to tell me that?
我们只是来吓吓你  仅此而已
We were just supposed to scare you, that's all.
那下次更狠一点
You try harder next time.
滚出去
Get out.
滚
Get out!
朱莉  进来吧
Oh, hey, Julie. Come on in.
我这有一些矶鹞渡的文件
I've got ‭those Sandpiper documents.
好  先放这吧
Great. Just put them anywhere.
霍华德说要你立刻处理
Howard asked if you could go through them now.
已经一点一刻了  我正要去吃午饭
It's 1:15. I was just about to grab some lunch.
两点半之前要处理好  他要用来起草文件
Yeah, he needs them done by 2:30 so he can draft a letter.
我带来了这个
I brought these.
我可以用备用金帮你点个外卖
Figured I could petty-cash a lunch order for you.
我得到财务的许可了  能从那家新沙拉店点餐
I got accounting to approve that new fancy salad place.
凯莉
Kaylee!
过来  别离泳池边太远
Come on, ‭not too far from the side.
把球丢过来  爷爷
Throw the ball, pop-pop!
我们什么时候回家
When are we going home?
怎么了  你不喜欢这里吗
What? You don't like it here?
还好吧
It's okay.
"还好"
"It's okay"?
你有个泳池呢  你还想要什么
You got a pool. What more do you want?
-好吧  -"好吧"
- I guess. - ‭You guess?
"好吧"
You guess?
你想出来吗
Well, you want to come out of there?
不  我要待在水里
No! I'm staying.
你想让我进去抱你上来吗
Well, you want me ‭to come in there and get you?
我可不能让你待在"还好"的池子里
I can't have you in a pool that's only okay.
很好  泳池很好
It's good, it's good!
你确定吗
You sure?
你确定
确定
I'm sure.
凯莉  宝贝  该出来了
Kaylee, honey, ‭it's time to come out now.
就再待一会儿
Just a few more minutes.
不行  听爷爷的话
No, you do what pop-pop says.
上来吧  宝贝
Come on, baby.
免得皮肤给泡皱了
Before you turn into a prune.
小姐
Miss?
那位先生让我告诉您
The gentleman ‭would like me to let you know
下一杯他请
that your next drink is on him.
您要点单了就叫我
Just let me know when you're ready.
我现在点
I'm ready.
不知道这招会管用
Wasn't sure that was gonna work.
别告诉我这是你第一次这样做
Don't tell me that's the first time you've done that.
那么  你用这杯酒作投资
So, what kind of return on investment
想得到什么样的回报呢
are you getting on these drinks?
什么都不如你
None as pretty as you.
天哪
Oh, man.
我是戴尔
I'm Dale, by the way.
吉赛尔
Giselle.
第四十四项
Okay, item number 44.
是什么
What do we have?
阿比盖尔·希尔德雷思的居住合同
Residency contract for Abigail Hildreth.
阿比盖尔·希尔德雷思
Abigail Hildreth.
什么时候签的
And what's the date on that?
一九九九年八月一日
Dated August 1, 1999.
August 1, 1999.
一九九九年八月一日
有希尔德雷思女士的相应证词吗
And do we have the corresponding deposition for Mrs. Hildreth?
有
Yes.
你没听过那句话吗
Have you ever heard the expression
"心急水不开"
"A watched pot never boils"?
在这呢
Oh. Here it is.
谢谢  看到没
Thank you. See?
归到第十二项了
I've got her down as item 12.
作证日期  九月十五日
Date of depo, September 15th.
九月十五日
September 15th.
15th of September.
九月十五日
September 15th.
没错就是九月十五日
Or, yeah, September 15th.
谢谢
Thank you.
第四十五项
Okay, item number 45.
吉米
Jimmy.
是我奶奶
Oh, it's my grandma.
她年纪大了
She's old.
我马上回来
Be right back.
金
Kim?
你最快什么时候能赶到城里
How fast can you get downtown?
圣达菲城里吗
Uh, Santa Fe Downtown?
-阿尔布开克  -为什么
- Albuquerque. ‭- Why?
我在福克餐厅的酒吧
I'm at the bar at Forque.
我钓到一条大鱼了
And I've got a live one on the hook.
我马上来
I'm on my way.
机会有多大
What's the shot?
绝对就两三个
Definitely two or three.
你觉得他们做不到吗
You don't think they do?
-你知道...  -他们行的
- Well, you know -- - ‭They could.
但是他们没必要啊
I know, ‭but they don't have to. ‭
我们知道
We get it.
的确有可能
It's possible,
但我不明白这有什么大不了的
but I don't understand why that's an issue.
-是啊  是啊  -总会出乱子的
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - It can always go bad.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah. ‭
-维克多  你来  -抱歉我迟到了
- Oh, Viktor, there you are. - So sorry I'm late.
-我刚好有急事  -不用介意
- I had to put out a few fires. - ‭Not a problem.
我交了个新朋友  戴尔  这是我哥哥维克多
I made a new friend. Dale, my brother, Viktor.
-你好吗  -很高兴认识你  戴尔
- Hey, how ya doing? - Oh, nice to meet you, Dale.
-谢谢你陪我妹妹  -不客气
- Thanks for ‭keeping sis company. - My pleasure.
你需要喝一杯
You need a drink.
来给你叫一杯
Let's get you a drink.
你是干什么的  戴尔
So, what do you do, Dale?
我是一名工程师
I'm an engineer.
就像凯西·琼斯那样的吗  戴帽子
What, like Casey Jones, with the hat and...
美国铁路工人  被誉为"勇敢的工程师"
不  傻蛋
No, idiot!
他是那种工程师  不是那种
An engineer engineer, not an "engineer."
戴尔是建东西的
Dale builds things.
我设计东西  主要是溢洪道和排水区域
I design things -- spillways and drainage fields, mostly.
其实都不是我造的
I don't -- I don't actually build them.
很厉害啊
Well, that's cool, yeah.
但你还是能戴帽子的吧
But you could still wear the hat, though, right?
没有什么能阻止你吧
I mean, nothin stoppin' ya.
是啊  应该可以
Oh, yeah, I guess I could.
据我所知  没有规定禁止你戴吧
I'm just saying, there's no rule about that, as far as I know.
你真是讨厌  怎么心情这么好
Hey, you're such a brat. Why the good mood?
今天...很顺利吗
Did it... go well today?
告诉我很顺利
Please tell me it went well.
是啊  很顺利
Yeah, it went well.
非常顺利吗  非常非常...
Very well? Like, very, very...?
远远超出我们的预期...
Beyond our wildest, uh...
太好了
Yeah.
她到底喝了几杯
How many of these has she had?
我才刚开始呢  宝贝
Mm! I am just getting started, baby.
-记住这两张脸  戴尔  -吉赛尔
- Remember these faces, Dale. - ‭Giselle.
我们将会亮相《财富》杂志一月封面
They are gonna be on the cover of Fortune magazine, January issue.
吉赛尔  别说了
‭Giselle, please.
不  戴尔是好人  没有恶意
No, Dale's a good guy. He's not gonna do anything.
-你让人家觉得无聊了  -不不不  没有
- Yeah, ‭you're boring the man. - Oh, no, no, not really.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧  我要去一趟厕所
All right, I am off to the little girl's room.
我不在的时候不准说我坏话
Say only nice things about me while I'm gone, okay?
她真漂亮
She's something.
是啊
Yeah.
吉赛尔告诉我你们俩在创业
So, Giselle was telling me you two are starting a business.
她到底怎么和你说的
What exactly did she tell you?
没说太多
Oh, nothing much.
就说了什么网站
Just something about a dot com,
让人们通过互联网交友
some way for people to hook up with each other using the internet?
我相信你是个好人
Oh, look, I'm sure you're a nice guy,
但她其实是乱说的
but she was talking out of school.
-我们...这个项目人满了  -好吧
- We're -- we're full up on this thing. - ‭Oh. Oh, okay.
我们再签下一名投资商
We sign one more investor,
就该上市了  我只是...
we got to go public, and I'm just...
不
No.
我们人已经满了
We cannot take anyone else on.
无意冒犯
No offense.
没关系
Oh, it's okay. Yeah.
不用担心
No worries.
张开手臂
Spread your arms.
他戴了窃听器吗
没有
No.
没有窃听器  但...
他有一把枪
He's got a gun.
带枪没关系
I don't care about the gun.
明天  你去找地检官
Tomorrow, ‭you go to the district attorney,
向他解释我侄子的枪是你的
and you explain to him that my nephew's gun was yours.
地检会问你
The D.A. will ask you,
"你为什么之前不说"
"Why you didn't say anything before?"
你跟他说你忘了  你吓坏了...
You tell him you forgot, you were rattled --
随便你编什么理由
Make up anything you want.
我不在乎
I don't give a shit.
但这是你的枪
But it's your gun.
我们来谈谈我的报酬吧
Let's discuss my payment.
晚了
Mm, that time is past.
五千块飞了
No $5,000 for you.
我要五万
The price is $50,000.
报酬是活着走出去怎么样
How about the payment is you get to live?
不够
Not enough.
你觉得你有资格跟我谈条件吗
Oh, you think ‭you can negotiate with me?
只要我一句话
I say the word,
我的侄子们就会去汽车旅馆
my nephews go to a certain motel,
拜访你的儿媳和你的小孙女
pay a visit to your daughter-in-law and your little granddaughter.
你觉得接下来会怎么样
What do you think happens then?
好好考虑考虑你的处境
Consider your position carefully.
要么给我钱
I get my money...
要么我俩都别想活着走出这里
or neither of us walk out of here.
你为了这个连命都不要了吗
You willing to die for this?
或许我比你更需要那五万块吧
Maybe I need the $50,000 more than you do.
我早说了吧
够胆儿
你说话这么欠是怎么活到现在的
How you manage to live so long with a mouth like that, hmm?
五万块
$50,000.
枪是你的
And the gun is yours.
他派你来的吗
He sent you?
我主动要来的
I volunteered.
只有这样说话才安全
Only safe way for us to talk.
你刚才在那太得寸进尺了
You really pushed it in there.
我们干的那事
That thing we did...
一旦被他发现  我们俩都必死无疑
...he finds out, we're both dead.
这你清楚的吧
You get that, right?
我们干什么了
What thing we did?
这是干嘛
What's this?
两万五
$25,000.
为什么要给我
What for?
我们达成了协议
We made a deal.
而我搞砸了
I didn't hold up my end.
你的麻烦很快就要回来了  比我们预计的更快
Your problem is coming back sooner than we expected.
克拉多克海事银行
大北极公司
你要把钱提出来吗
You gonna cash that?
我认识个人  他或许能帮忙
I might know a guy who can help.
还是把它当成纪念品吧
It's better as a souvenir.
我以为你今天早上可能会  我也不知道
I figured you'd be maybe -- I don't know --
稍微开心一点
a touch happier this morning.
就算只有那么一点点
Maybe a smidge, possibly?
我很开心  非常开心
I am. I'm totally happy.
为什么会不开心
Why wouldn't I be?
我
I, uh...
我收到了一份工作邀请
I had a job offer.
真的吗  哪家律所
Really? From where?
斯韦卡特考科利
Schweikart and Cokely.
真的假的
Seriously?
里奇·斯韦卡特甚至还说愿意帮我偿还
Rich Schweikart said that they would even pay off
法学院的贷款
my law-school loans.
太棒了
That's great.
你向霍华德辞职的时候请叫上我
Please let me be there when you tell Howard.
拜托了
Please.
那为什么还一脸忧伤
So why the sad puppy eyes?
你不想要那个工作吗
What, you don't want that job?
不不  我当然想要
No, no, o-of course I do.
谁会拒绝这样的机会  是吧
I mean, who wouldn't, right?
这是家大律所
It's a huge firm.
你再也不用在霍华德手下受气
You get out ‭from under Howard's thumb.
是啊  就是
Right. Exactly.
反正我在哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
Besides, HHM is looking more and more like
越来越没有前途
a dead end for me, anyway.
就是啊  所以还有什么问题吗
Exactly. So what's the problem?
我只是
I just...
我也不知道
I don't know.
我一直在想你漂在那个池子里的场景
I keep thinking of you floating in that pool.
你知道你想要什么  可我成了你的障碍
You knew what you wanted, but I got in the way.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你进戴维斯梅因律所是为了我
You took the Davis & Main job because of me.
我去那里工作是因为这是正确的决定
I took that job because it was the right decision.
稳定的收入  有了
A steady paycheck -- done.
比原来不知道大到哪里去的住处  也有了
A place to live that's more than, oh, 5 square feet -- boom.
纯色的汽车  到手了
A car that's all one color -- nailed it.
我日子很好过
‭I'm good.
我得到了我想要的
I got what I wanted.
等你进了斯韦卡特
And you, ‭with the Schweikart thing?
你就可以得到你想要的一切
You could have ‭everything you ever wanted.
还有什么不满意的
What's not to love about that?
是啊
Yeah.
还有什么不满意的
What's not to love?